(Howard:)What was I supposed to talk about?
We were eating at Johnny Rockets.
(Bernadette:)Just saying people
are getting a little tired of it.
(Howard:)So I did this amazing thing
and I'm never allowed to mention it?
(Bernadette:)Of course you can. But, maybe a good rule
would be to wait for people to bring it up.
Okay, heh. No problem.
It won't happen again.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
(Howard:)I can't tell you how many times...
(Howard:)...I dreamed I was in bed here...
(Howard:)...with you when I was...
(Raj:)You know...
(Howard:)What, I can't even point?
(Leonard:)So, basically,
this is what's called mag-lev technology.
It uses powerful electromagnets to create
a force strong enough to overcome gravity.